DUNG. PHAM QUAN TIEN

github.com/tiendung1510 linkedin.com/in/dungpqt

Backend Developer | Fullstack Developer

SUMMARY

Versatile full-stack developer with experience across diverse company environments, from startups to major corporations. Demonstrated ownership and can-do attitude, excelling in both independent and collaborative projects. Committed to delivering high-quality results in fast-paced settings, combining technical expertise with a strong work ethic. Continuously staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends.

SKILLS

Languagues: Java, Javascript, SQL, Typescript, Go.

Frameworks: Spring Boot, Node.js, , Nest.js, React.js, Ant.design, Tailwind.css.
Other tools: MySQL, Redis, ELK, Kafka, Docker, Nginx, Grafana, Prometheus.

• Communication: Vietnamese, English.

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Backend Engineer Nov 2022 - Now

Binance - Card Promotion team

Remote

- Led a project to design and develop new promotion where users will get cashback when they make their first transaction using Binance card and save their card information for future transactions.
- Participated in a new promotion that allow users buy discounted items with their Binance Card, it helped Binance attract more than 5 times the number of card orders per day during this promotion period.
- Built a reminder framework that makes it easier to send notifications at a future time, which is used to send most types of reminders in my team's projects.

Java Spring Boot Dubbo RPC MySQL Kafka Redis ELK Grafana Docker Unit Test

Backend Engineer

Aug 2022 - Sep 2022

Shopee, Sea Group - Marketplace Intelligence team

Singapore

• Worked at the Marketplace Intelligence team but got laid off after 4 weeks of working here because of the difficult financial situation of Sea Group. I put the name here because it still a big achievement for me.

Go gRPC MySQL Kafka Redis ELK Grafana Docker

Senior Fullstack Developer

Apr 2021 - July 2022

MCVGo, MCV Group (Startup) - Core team

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

- Built a real-time interactive system to organize gaming sessions like Kahoot, and Confetti (Facebook), which can scale horizontally and handle 10k concurrent players on a server with 8GB RAM, 4vCPU
- Built an IAM system that supports SSO, and central role/permission management based on Keycloak for internal admin tools which can easy to integrate and save a lot of team development time.
- Built a notification system that supports in-app, firebase notification and can scale horizontally using Spring Boot, Kafka, and Redis.
- Set up CI/CD using Github actions, logging using ELK, and reverse proxy/load balancing using Nginx.

Java Spring Boot Akka MySQL Kafka Redis ELK Docker Nginx HTML/CSS/JS React.js

Backend Developer

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021

LINE Corporation - Backend team

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

- Built a crawler that helps moderators easily identify invalid ads links by taking a picture of the link's destination and checking the number of redirects using puppeteer.
- Built a worker that maps millions of raw data a day on user feedback about LINE ads to output some meaningful metrics (in the ML field) using stream processing and batch update methodology.

(Java)	Spring	a Boot	MvSQL) (Kafka	Redis) (Node.i	s)(Nest.i	s (Puppeteer	•) (Crawler
--------	--------	--------	-------	----------	-------	-----------	-----------	--------------	-------	---------

Fullstack Developer

Oct 2018 - Sep 2020

VNG Corporation - Zalo team

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

- Built an SSO system based on OAuth flow and Zalo's social login API for internal admin tools.
- Built an SSH permission management system, which manages SSH of hundred developers on 1200 servers.
- Built a logging tool like Kibana's discover, which consume millions of log a day and have an easy-to-use UI using Servlet and Elasticsearch.
- Built <u>docs.zalopay.vn</u> an API specification and integration documentation using JAM stack.

Go Gin Java Servlet MySQL Redis HTML/CSS/JS React.js Ant.design

ACHIVEMENTS

• Third prize, WebDev Hackathon (University of Information Technology, Vietnam).

Jun 2019

• Second prize, Olympiad in Informatics for Vietnamese students.

Nov 2017

• Second prize, Olympiad in Informatics for HCMUS students.

Nov 2017

EDUCATION

University of Science

Oct 2016 - Sep 2022

Infomration Technology, GPA: 8.52/10

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam